How do enemies find common ground?
Oslo is a tv movie, drama, history film directed by Bartlett Sher.
The true story of negotiations between implacable enemies — the secret back-channel talks, unlikely friendships and quiet heroics of a
small but committed group of Israelis, Palestinians and one Norwegian couple that led to the 1993 Oslo Peace Accords.
Mona Juul, played by Ruth Wilson.
Terje Rød-Larsen, played by Andrew Scott.
Ahmed Qurei, played by Salim Daw.
Hassan Asfour, played by Waleed Zuaiter.
Uri Savir, played by Jeff Wilbusch.
Joel Singer, played by Igal Naor.
Oslo is a 2021 American political drama television film about
the secret negotiation of the Oslo Accords.
The film was directed by Bartlett Sher and written by J.
Rogers, based on Rogers' play of the same name.
It stars Andrew Scott, Ruth Wilson, and Jeff Wilbusch.
It was released on May 29, 2021, on HBO.
The film explores themes of based on true story,
based on play or musical, 1990s.
The tone is emotional.